[EP09]
Young Marshal.
Get lost.
Yes, sir.
Why didn't you dodge?
I've returned
the bullet I owed you.
What a madman!
You really shot me.
I'm not your family doctor.
If you want me to dress your wound next time,
I'll charge you.
The suicide note.
It's in the drawer over there.
Why do you have it?
Zhao Yue brought it here after you fainted.
You can't drink with an external wound.
If you want to die of tetanus one day,
you can tell me in advance.
I'll laugh at your grave.
The pistol is for you.
Take it for self-defense.
[My son,]
[when you read this letter,]
[I will no longer be here.]
[In such a turbulent world,]
[don't dwell on past grievances.]
[I hope my departure]
[can bring back]
[the happiness you should have.]
[Ling Shenxing is taciturn,]
[but he's a good man.]
[In this turbulent world,]
[only he can protect you.]
[Only he can protect you.]
[Take care.]
Mom,
we finally met.
How can you leave me?
Her mother's suicide is suspicious.
It must be related to the banned drug.
Zhao Yue
must know something.
I didn't expect Zhao Yue to commit suicide.
According to Zhao Yue's family,
she followed her mother
and hanged herself.
In my opinion,
the strangulation mark
on the neck of a person who hanged himself
should only have one strangulation mark.
But there are two strangulation marks
on her neck.
It's obvious that she was strangled to death by someone else,
and then hung up to make it look like a suicide.
I noticed that
there was some skin tissue under her fingernails.
According to your thoughts,
if that's the case,
the skin tissue
was likely left by the murderer during the struggle.
By the way, brother,
Zhao Yue doesn't use perfume, does she?
I detected a fragrance on her body.
Mother didn't like incense,
and Zhao Yue was her personal maid.
She definitely wouldn't use perfume.
I suspect the one who killed Zhao Yue
is the one who harmed our Su family.
Brother,
we have to investigate
one by one.
I want to know who Mother met
before I went to the Su Family.
Don't worry,
I'll find out the truth.
Wan'er,
when I'm not around,
take care of yourself.
Don't worry, brother.
I'll listen to mother.
I'll live well.
Take this.
Hongxiu, how can you afford such good medicine?
It's already a great kindness that you saved me from the killer.
And you protect me here.
I...
Just take it.
Thank you, Young Marshal.
Do you know this?
This is
the jade pendant of the head of the Su Family.
Young Marshal,
how is my young lady?
my young lady is kind and gentle,
and has deep feelings for you.
She got along with Young Master Chu
only because Chu Nanfeng told her
that she knew you well.
I don't know if the General and Madam
sold prohibited drugs,
but my lady truly knows nothing.
There's no Miss Su here,
only Madam Ling.
So Su Muwan does have feelings for me.
Mr. Chu,
what can I do for you?
I heard
Commander Ling is back.
I have a small gift here.
I want you to give it to him.
Chu Nanfeng said that Ling Shenxing planned the Su family's business.
But I don't believe anyone.
OK.
I'll give it to him.
I've heard about your mother.
If you feel sad,
don't force yourself.
Thank you for your concern.
If there's nothing else,
I'll go.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
Are you alright?
I'm having
an unlucky year.
I'm sorry to let you see this.
Let me help you.
Rickshaw.
I'll take you back.
Put me down.
It's not proper.
I don't
have so many rules as you do.
And your ankle is hurt.
I can't let you limp
into the door.
If you are in a hurry to get married,
there are plenty of marriageable women in Yang City.
You don't have to try so hard in my family.
Let me go.
Oh my god.
They're at it again.
They'll draw their guns if this goes on.
I need to find a way to get out of here.
Young Marshal,
I sprained my ankle.
Please take me home.
Xiao Wan,
if you want to go out for a walk,
just come to me.
Okay.
Xiao Wan.
Young Master Chu, please go back.
My wife doesn't need your concern.
Ling Shenxing, just wait.
The position of Su Muwan and Young Marshal
will be mine sooner or later.
Only when I become the Young Marshal
and have power,
can I do what I want to do.